

Batuhan TURGUT

Date of birth: 19/08/2002

Nationality: Turkish

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Kosova Mahallesi, Balarası Sokak No:10E, Garden Park Evleri, No: 11 42250 Konya, Turkey

iletisim@batuhanturgut.com.t r

(+90) 5060673390

http://batuhanturgut.com.tr/

LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ batuhanturgut43/

Other: https://github.com/

betaisyn5243



ABOUT ME

I'm Batuhan Turgut. I got interested in programming in high school. with Java

I continued on this path that I started by dealing with Java and Cyber Security for 4 years. I started exploring other technologies besides just using Java. In this process, I developed projects on many languages at the beginner-intermediate level. I am experienced in OOP, MVC AND REST api architecture. I was interested in the future and flexibility of JavaScript and I discovered Node.js, React Native, Vue, Angular technologies. The package structure of React Native caught my attention and I saw that it provides Cross Platform Development. I have been developing freelance sites for over a year using React/Node.js, React/Spring, React/Django.

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/06/2020 – 20/06/2020 – İzmir, Turkey

Freelance Developer

Data Scraping with Selenium

Data gathering on Exchange platforms

01/08/2020 - 08/08/2020 - Selçuklu, Turkey

Freelance Developer

WordPress

Preparing end-user ready web-sites with a database connected to a ready-made template and a server set.

21/09/2020 - 30/09/2020 - İzmir, Turkey

Freelance Developer

Data Scraping with Node.js

Data gathering on Weather API and processing after creating RESTful API

20/09/2021 - 01/11/2021 - İzmir, Turkey

Freelance Developer

Java GUİ programming with JFX

Desktop application for photo processing in accordance with the wishes of the client.

25/11/2021 - 25/12/2021 - Konya, Turkey

Freelance Developer

Cross-Platform App Development with Flutter

Data gathering on IMDB Movie API, Facebook login with Firebase

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

27/10/2020 - CURRENT - Konya, Turkey

Computer Engineering

Selçuk University

25/09/2016 - 05/06/2020 - İzmir, Turkey



LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Turkish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening Reading Spoken Spoken Writing
B2 C1 production interaction B1
A2 B1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Flutter/Dart / C# / Java / Python / C++

Front-end

HTML5 / CSS / JavaScript

MERN stack

express.js / MongoDB / React.js / Node.js

Toolkit

Git / Docker / Linux / RESTful api / SQL

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Cyber Security

Web, Desktop apps, Penetration testing

Photography

Badminton

Automation

Automate the things i do daily